普契尼歌剧
蝴蝶夫人
安德伍德国际
戴维营
白宫观察
华盛顿爆发抗议  沃克总统未表态
梅杰·加勒特
CBS新闻网首席白宫记者
白宫观察
华盛顿爆发抗议  沃克总统未表态
斯科特·瑟曼
ABC七台新闻组
艾拉·萨伊德
《华尔街电讯报》
斯科特·瑟曼
ABC七台新闻组
艾拉·萨伊德
《华尔街电讯报》
斯科特·瑟曼
ABC七台新闻组
艾拉·萨伊德
《华尔街电讯报》
重大新闻
副总统抵达戴维营
总统先生收
我们的总统不仅服用精神药物
We have a president who not only took mind-altering medication --
当美国舰队与中国对峙时
a man who has his finger on the button
他可以随时批准实施打击
while U.S. Ships are squaring off with China --
还授意他的白宫顾问去干预...
but then instructed his White House counsel to coach a --
据称  先生  没有被证实
Allegedly, sir. Not proven.
去干预证人  他的做法
To coach a witness. Which is behavior either resulting
要么是受药物影响  要么更糟
from the use of those drugs, or worse,
是有意想践踏法律
a deliberate attempt to obstruct the law.
你不觉得两种情况都该被弹劾吗
Now wouldn't you call either scenario impeachable?
那该由国会决定  先生  而不是我
That's for the United States Congress to decide, sir. Not me.
你知道总统在服用任何药物吗
Were you aware that the president was taking any form of medication?
不  我不知道
No, I was not.
你注意到他举止古怪吗
Did you notice him acting in a bizarre fashion?
-情绪不稳  语无伦次  -没有  先生
- Unstable, incoherent? - No, sir.
-有任何奇怪的行为吗  -没有  先生
- Any odd behavior? - No, sir.
在贸易战之际解雇幕僚长不算吗
Not even firing his chief of staff in the midst of a trade war?
他没有解雇我  是我主动辞职的
He didn't fire me. I resigned.
你能告诉我们为什么吗
Would you tell us why?
我辞职是因为我觉得自己无法
I resigned because I felt I could no longer
再以最好的状态为总统服务
serve the president to the best of my ability.
发生了什么变化  是什么让你得出那样的结论
And what changed? How did you come to that conclusion?
我与白宫中的某些人
I had some fundamental differences of opinion
基本理念不合
with certain people in the White House.
比如谁  总统吗
Like who? The president?
不  先生
No, sir.
那某些人是指谁
Well, what certain people then?
实际上只有一个人
One person, actually.
副总统  弗兰克·安德伍德
The vice president, Frank Underwood.
他想让你离开吗
He wanted you gone?
我不敢说副总统想怎么样  不想怎么样
I can't speak as to what the vice president did or didn't want.
他想要隐藏什么吗
Was he trying to hide anything?
他是不是怕你曝光什么
Was he afraid you might expose something?
那你得去问他  先生
You'd have to ask him, sir.
司法委员会正在上演的是一出闹剧
What's happening in the Judiciary Committee is a farce.
共和党正在利用这种...
The Republicans are exploiting the situ--
插一句  副总统先生
Excuse me, Mr. Vice President,
不仅仅是共和党
but it's not just Republicans.
不少民主党人也站出来说
A number of Democrats have come out saying
他们支持弹劾
they would support impeachment.
包括多数党党鞭  杰姬·夏普
Including the Majority Whip, Jackie Sharp.
这令人发指
Which is egregious,
因为委员会还在进行听证
since the committee hasn't stopped hearing testimony,
特别检察官也没有完成调查
and nor has the special prosecutor completed her investigation.
你极力维护总统
You vigorously defend the president,
但有报道称你们已经闹僵
but there are reports that you've had a falling out.
你们好几个星期没说过话了
That you haven't spoken in weeks.
一派胡言
That is simply not true.
我与白宫的高级官员通过话
I've spoken to senior staff at the White House
他说总统担心你会在2016年大选中与他竞争
who say the president is worried you want to run against him in 2016.
而就在今天  琳达·瓦斯奎兹暗指你...
And just today Linda Vasquez intimated that you --
我相信总统一定会在2016年竞选连任
Look, I fully expect that the president will run in 2016,
而且我希望他能够慷慨地邀请我
and I hope he's generous enough to invite me
作他的竞选伙伴
to be his running mate.
弹劾  定罪  如果是这个结果呢
Impeachment, conviction. Let's say it happens.
不会的  他完全是无辜的
It won't. He's completely innocent.
我们假设一下  你成了总统
Let's say it does happen. You become president.
我不会去想象那个情形
That is not a scenario I'm going to entertain.
但你脑中肯定有过这个想法
But the thought must have crossed your mind.
而且可以说  如果不是因为你
And one could make the argument that the president
总统也不会陷入这样的窘境
wouldn't be in this predicament if it weren't for you.
是你的幕僚长与冯和拉尼根的牵连
It's your staff's involvement with Feng and Lanagin
才引发了邓巴的调查
that expanded Dunbar's investigation,
-随之发现了出行记录  -这些弹劾听证
- which resulted in the travel logs - Look, these impeachment hearings
是政治操纵的结果
are the result of political maneuvering,
-而不是  -是你在操纵还是共和党
- not the fact that-- - Your maneuverings, or the Republicans?
莫里  我一直很喜欢你  你的问题很尖锐
Morley, I've always liked you. You ask the tough questions.
你当然可以质疑我的判断
And you can certainly question my judgment.
但不要质疑我的爱国心
But do not question my patriotism.
我为国家和总统服务  而不是我自己
I serve this nation and my president, not myself.
他满口谎言
He's lying through his teeth.
我们所做的已经见效了
What we're doing is working.
让大家一直私下谈论
We keep the whisper campaign alive.
我们让他显得渴望权利  显得奸诈
We spin him as power-hungry, as duplicitous.
将焦点集中在他身上  而不是您
Focus attention on him. Not you.
最新支持率是多少  20%吗
What's the latest? 20%?
佐格比的数据是24%  您的讲话起了作用
Zogby has you at 24. Your speech made a difference.
支持率正在上升
The approval numbers are moving in the right direction.
我们不能再这么小打小闹了
We need to do more than play the spin game.
我们要打垮弗兰克  让他而不是我去当牺牲品
We need to destroy Frank. Offer his head instead of mine.
-我们利用雷蒙德·塔斯克  -怎么利用
- We use Raymond Tusk. - How?
在他的听证会上  在他去司法委员会时
At his hearing. When he goes to the Judiciary.
先生  您已经被指控干预一个证人了
Sir, you're already being accused of coaching one witness.
如果您再干预另一...
If you take steps to coach anoth--
不是干预  是让他说出事实
Not coaching. The truth.
雷蒙德承认洗钱
Raymond admits to the money laundering,
把弗兰克推到风口浪尖  说我什么都不知道
puts Frank at the center of this, and says I knew nothing.
之后我们会回报他的诚实
And then we'll reward him for his honesty.
您是说特赦吗
You mean a pardon.
我想让你跟他去谈
I want you to talk to him.
让我自己陷于危险之中吗
And put myself at risk?
你现在不在政府供职了
Well, you're not part of this administration anymore.
没有法律规定你不能去拜访雷蒙德·塔斯克
There's no law that says you can't pay Raymond Tusk a visit.
作为回报  辞职也不非得永久有效  琳达
And in return, resignations don't have to last forever, Linda.
如果我这么做  您得和我保持距离  越远越好
If I do this, you have to be a million miles away.
特莉莎和我会去戴维营
Tricia and I'll go to Camp David.
不算特别远  但也够了
It's not a million miles away, but it'll do the job.
我可以对琳达下手  调查她的过去
I can go after Linda. Dig into her past --
搞定她解决不了大问题
Neutralizing her won't neutralize the bigger problem.
是总统想要我的命
It's the president that's after blood.
那他打算怎么做
Then what's his move?
他不能要求我辞职  只能把我挤走
He can't ask me to resign. He'd have to force me out.
要挤走我的话  如果我是他
And to do that, if I were him,
肯定会回去找最初成就我的人
I would return to the hand that first fed me.
-雷蒙德·塔斯克吗  -没错
- Raymond Tusk? - Exactly.
不会  他要是把你卷进去  他自己也难保
No, he'd have to implicate himself to implicate you.
除非他能得到赦免
Not if he gets a pardon.
这是唯一只有总统才能开出的条件
It's the one thing that only a president can offer.
塔斯克是个手榴弹  如果他赦免了他...
Tusk is a hand grenade. If he pardons him --
没错  塔斯克是个手榴弹
You're right. Tusk is a hand grenade,
我们得拽下保险栓  朝沃克扔过去
and we need to pull the pin and throw him at Walker
否则就是沃克拽下保险栓  扔向我们了
before Walker pulls the pin and throws him at us.
我得和雷蒙德见面  一对一
I want to meet with Raymond, one on one.
我代表你去谈吧
Let me speak on your behalf.
-这样的话  如果有人发现  -我了解雷蒙德
- That way if anyone finds -- -I know Raymond.
他只会对我做出回应
He won't respond to anyone but me.
他的听证会安排在什么时候
When's his hearing scheduled?
后天下午两点
Uh, day after tomorrow. Two p.m.
-那我们还有40个小时行动  -是  先生
- That gives us 40 hours to make it happen. - Yes, sir.
可能是我的手机
I think it's mine.
赛斯  现在可是凌晨四点
Seth, it's four in the morning.
什么时候
When?
我希望你跟她一起去
I want you to go with her.
-我这就去征求洛克兰的批准  -谢谢
- I'll get it cleared with Rockland right now. -Thank you.
密查姆说飞机30分钟内就能准备好
Meechum says the plane will be ready in 30 minutes.
行  好
Okay, good.
你觉得只是恐慌症发作
You think it was just a panic attack
-还是她真打算...  -我不知道
- or was she really trying -- -I don't know.
他们要她留院观察一整夜就够糟了
It was bad enough they felt they had to keep her overnight.
我给白宫医生办公室打个电话
I'm gonna call the White House physician's office,
-看看他们能不能推荐什么人 -好
- see if they can recommend anyone. - Okay.
-等等  我的手机  -在你手里
- Oh, wait. My phone. - It's in your hand.
我今晚回来
I'll be back sometime tonight.
弹劾是我们唯一的机会
Impeachment is our only chance.
这些席位在中期选举中仍处于争夺状态
Here are the seats that are still in contention in the midterms.
这13个我们再怎么努力也会失去
These 13 we're gonna lose no matter what we do.
但即便我们拿下剩下所有席位
But even if we win all the rest,
我们也只有五个席位的优势
that only leaves us with a five-seat majority.
要么保党  要么保总统
We either save the party or we save the president.
任何人反对弹劾的人
Anyone who votes against impeachment
在选举前都会受到攻击性广告的攻击
is gonna get pommeled by attack ads between now and election day.
你已经有多少票了
How many do you have already?
我们需要18票  我只有六票
We need 18. I have six.
那还要争取12票
So, 12 more to go.
唐纳德  我知道这是个很大的人情
Look, Donald, I know this is a big ask
你更想把注意力放在政策上  不...
and you prefer to focus on policy and not --
杰姬  不用说了  我加入
Jackie, you can stop. I'm on board.
-真的吗  - 百分百
- Really? - 100%.
不得不说  我有点惊讶
I have to say I'm a little surprised.
你把那些手推车推进休息室的时候  你说
When you rolled those dollies into the cloakroom you said,
"跟我合作  我不是弗兰克·安德伍德"
"Work with me. I'm not Frank Underwood."
然后你帮我通过了经济刺激方案
And then you helped get my stimulus package through,
你信守了诺言
just like you promised.
这次你有什么期望呢
And what do you expect this time?
我希望你永远不会成为弗兰克·安德伍德
That you never become Frank Underwood.
你要知道  如果我们成功了  他会取代沃克
You must realize if we're successful, he will replace Walker.
我不喜欢弗兰克  但我更讨厌成为少数党
I don't like Frank. but I hate being in the minority even more.
我们不能让共和党同时执掌国会两院
We can't let the Republicans control both houses of Congress.
我加入领导层以来  你变了
You've changed since I joined the leadership.
只是更懂得如何玩这场游戏了
Just getting better at playing the game.
看来顽固不化这词不太对
I guess you can teach an old liberal new tricks.
看来是的
I guess so.
告诉我你还需要谁
So, tell me who you still need.
我的律师说我赢得庭审的概率是一半一半
My lawyers are saying 50/50 that I survive a trial.
我不太满意这个数字
Now, I'm not a big fan of those odds,
但我愿意接受
but I'm willing to take 'em.
如果你的律师说这事就看运气
If your lawyers are putting it at a coin toss,
那你是花钱雇了一群太过乐观的人
then you're paying them too much to be overly optimistic.
我怎么能信任加勒特
And how can I trust Garrett?
他背叛了20年的友谊
He turned his back on 20 years of friendship.
他也可以这么说你
He could accuse you of the same.
这地球上没有人
Well, nobody on this planet
比我更想看弗兰克·安德伍德进监狱了
wants to see Frank Underwood go to jail more than I do.
我只是不想到时跟他关在一起
I just don't want to be sharing a cell with him.
这种事不会发生的
That won't happen.
你只给了我加勒特的口头承诺
All you've given me to go on is Garrett's word.
他想让你说出实情
He's asking you to tell the truth.
做正确的事的人必有好报
Good things happen to those who do the right thing.
你们就指望弗兰克会跪地求饶
And you just expect Frank to lie down,
举旗认输吗
throw in the towel, hmm?
连求饶的机会也不给他
We don't even give him the chance.
你的证词会让他全无反击之力
Your testimony knocks him out cold.
请稍等
Excuse me.
什么事  啊  多谢你
Yes? Oh, thank you.
请等一下
Hold on.
给你
There you go.
我妻子送的小礼物
Care package from my wife.
那么  请继续
Now, you were saying.
我得提醒你一下  她现在完全不在状态
I just want to warn you, she's not herself right now.
他们不得不给她服用了大剂量的药物
They had to put her on some heavy doses.
什么药
Of what?
主要是碳酸锂[抗躁狂药]
Lithium, mostly.
不然就得留院观察30天了
It was either that or commit her for 30 days.
她刚吃了药  可能有点...
Now she just took some, so she might be a little...
梅根
Megan?
别碰我
Stop.
你妈妈告诉我他们从湖里救起了你
Your mom told me they found you in the lake.
你管我呢
What do you care?
我非常关心你
I care very much.
才怪
No, you don't.
没人会利用他们关心的人
You don't use somebody you care about.
娼妓
Whore.
荡妇
Slut.
婊子
Bitch.
叛徒
Traitor.
他们就是这么说我的
That's what they call me.
发邮件  在网上
In my mail. Online.
真希望我没打那通电话
I wish I'd never called.
真希望我没见过你
I wish I'd never met you.
你说什么我信什么  真是蠢透了
I feel so stupid believing what you told me.
我还以为你真心关心我
Thinking that you did care.
我本来都快恢复了
I was getting better.
这全怨你
You did this to me.
我每吃一片药  都会想到他
Every time I take one of these I think of him.
接下来我想到的
And the next face I think of?
就是你
It's yours.
你觉得被利用了  我很遗憾
I'm sorry that you felt used.
我没有利用你
You weren't.
我只是
I just, um...
就像我说的  政治风向变了  而且
like I told you, the political landscape shifted and --
而我们发现
and we found...
梅根
Megan?
你好
Hello?
我收到你的短信了
I got your text.
我知道我不该联系你  但我觉得
I know I shouldn't be reaching out to you, but I thought...
不  没关系  我很高兴你通知了我
No, that doesn't matter. I'm glad you did.
她怎么样
How is she?
状态很不好
In bad shape.
说实话我很吃惊他们还敢让她离开医院
I'm surprised they even let her out of the hospital, to be honest.
有什么我能做的吗
Is there anything I can do?
用不用我联系她的亲人  亲自去探望她
Should I contact her family or go out there myself?
我们最好不要打扰她了
We should probably leave her alone.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我没事  你呢
I'm fine. How about you?
还撑得住
Uh, holding up.
和律师商量了一整天
Spent the whole day talking to lawyers.
这对孩子们太不容易了
It's hard on the kids.
他们既窘迫又害怕
They're embarrassed and frightened.
但我们会熬过去的
But we'll get through it.
我觉得你和加勒特的讲话很感人
I thought the speech you and Garrett gave was very moving.
似乎起了点作用
Well, it seems to have helped some.
其实我是受你的启发
I was inspired by you, actually.
你敢于在电视上承认堕过胎
When you admitted to the abortion on TV.
真相往往很有冲击力
The truth is a powerful thing.
特莉莎  我想向你道歉
Tricia, I want to apologize.
为什么
What for?
你的家庭所经历的这些变故
I feel partly responsible for everything
我觉得我有一部分责任
your family's going through.
是我建议你们去见咨询师
It was my suggestion that you get counseling.
早知今日  我当初就什么都不会说了
And had I known then, I never would have said a word.
克莱尔  别这么说  见咨询师效果很好
Claire, please. Counseling was a godsend.
加勒特和我需要帮助
Garrett and I needed help,
而且也确实起了作用
and it's made things better.
我应该感谢你
I should be thanking you.
还要感谢你把梅根的事告诉我
And thank you for letting me know about Megan.
你能去看她  真是好心
It was kind of you to make that trip.
你是个好人  克莱尔
You're a good person, Claire.
保重
Be well.
我估计你是想说听证会的事
I take it this is about my hearing.
是不是沃克联系过你了
Did Walker get to you first?
没比你快多少
Barely.
但有时候  哪怕只快一点也足够了
But sometimes barely is enough.
他肯定提出给你特赦
I'm sure he offered you a pardon.
提供竞争对手给不了的  才是高招
Always better to offer something your competitor can't.
但我能给你更好的
Oh, but I can.
据我所知  宪法规定的
The last time I read the Constitution,
副总统能给的最有价值的东西也就是...
the most a vice president could offer was, um,
陪陪笑脸  递递眼色了
smile and a wink.
我想我已经证明我不是一般的副总统
I think I've proven that I'm not your typical vice president.
一般或不一般  你都输了  弗兰克
Typical or not, you've lost, Frank.
我还有出路  你没有
I have an out. You don't.
加勒特撑不过弹劾的
Garrett will not survive impeachment.
你绝不能否认
If there's one skill you can't deny,
我拉选票的能力
it's my ability to whip votes.
那是在众议院  不是在参议院
In the House. Not in the Senate.
但依据宪法  我是参议院的主席
Which the Constitution makes me the President of.
你也看到我是怎么通过福利改革了
And you saw what I did with entitlement.
傲慢使你自以为了不起了  弗兰克
Hubris is giving you delusions of grandeur, Frank.
就算沃克侥幸逃过一劫
Let's say Walker squeaks by.
是的  你能得到特赦
Yes, you get your pardon.
但你却把自己跟一个
But you've bound yourself at the hip
没有任何政治资本的人拴在一起了
to a man who has zero political capital.
如果他被定罪  我们都要坐牢
And if he gets convicted, we all go to jail.
谁都没有特赦了
There's no pardon for anyone.
我愿意赌一把
I'll roll the dice.
雷蒙德  用你的商业头脑想想
Raymond, think like a businessman.
你不就是靠尽量减小风险积累财富的吗
Haven't you built a fortune by minimizing risk?
这不就是你这些年用钱堆砌国会
Isn't that why you stacked Congress all these years,
引领加勒特当上总统
why you guided Garrett to the Oval,
留我当党鞭的原因吗
and why you kept me on as Whip?
沃克是个垃圾股  贬值得快
Walker is a junk bond quickly depreciating,
而我可以迅速解决和中国的贸易战
whereas I can end the conflict with China
还能保你不坐牢
and keep you in the black.
你没法保证改善和中国的关系
You can't promise better relations with China.
我破坏的  我也能修复
I wrecked them. I can repair them.
一起合作吧  就如我们起初打算的那样
Now let's work together, as we always intended to do.
等你被关进棺材大的牢房里
When they put you in that box barely bigger than a coffin,
记住今晚这美妙的音乐吧
remember how beautiful the music was tonight.
或许能让你稍微好受点
It might give you some small degree of comfort.
普契尼太伤感  我喜欢积极向上的
Puccini's a downer. I prefer something much more optimistic.
他们不肯放布朗  审判日期已经定了
They won't touch Brown. The trial date is set.
他们可以减少指控
They can reduce the charges.
达拉斯不愿让步  如果我继续施压
Dallas won't give. If I keep pressing,
会显得可疑
it'll start to look suspect.
我能确保你不被起诉
What I can do is make sure you don't get prosecuted.
还有我不再替你工作
And I stop working for you.
不全是  我跟检察官说
Not quite. I told the U.S. Attorney
我们想让你为我们工作
that we wanted to bring you on with us.
网络恐怖主义分局  你的案底将一笔勾销
Cyber terrorism division. You'd get a clean slate, as --
门都没有
No fucking way.
他们不会就那么放弃你
They're not gonna let your case go
除非我们给他们充分的理由
unless we give them a compelling reason.
-没别的  -我跟调查局斗争了半辈子
- There's no o - I've spent half my life fighting the Bureau.
我只能这么说
It's the only way I could sell it.
抓住机会  嘉文
Take this opportunity, Gavin,
趁他们还没改主意
before they change their minds.
我要见道格拉斯·斯坦普
I want to meet with Douglas Stamper.
不行  我们说好了我帮你找出路
No. The deal was I find you a way out.
说好的是你帮布朗脱身并且还我自由
No, the deal was you help out Brown and you give me my freedom.
你没为布朗办成任何事
You haven't done shit for Brown,
还想继续控制我
and you still want to keep me under your thumb.
让我见斯坦普  否则一切免谈
So I meet Stamper, or any kinda deal is off.
雷蒙德没答应
Raymond said no.
他没表态
He said neither yes nor no.
我会继续施压
I'll keep the pressure on.
他还是有可能指证你
So he could still name you.
是的  一切皆有可能
He could. Anything's possible.
你得阻止他
Well, you have to stop him.
我在尝试
I'm trying.
尝试远远不够  弗兰西斯
Well, trying's not enough, Francis.
我总不能在听证会上坐在他旁边
Well, I can't sit next to him in the hearing room
拿枪抵着他头
with a gun to his head.
这听起来像在找借口
Now that sounds like an excuse.
事实就是这样
It's a reality.
你答应过  我不用做最坏的打算
You promised me I wasn't going to have to prepare for the worst.
我也打算信守诺言
And I intend to keep that promise.
我想确保  我们都要确定会没事
Well, I want to be sure. I want both of us to be sure.
唯一万无一失的办法  就是让沃克阻止他
The only surefire way is for Walker to call him off personally.
那就去办
Then make that happen.
我不能逼一个拿我当敌人的人
I cannot force a man who thinks I'm his enemy
突然把我当朋友
to suddenly call me his friend.
我该做的都做了
I've done what I had to do.
现在轮到你了
Now you do what you have to do.
勾引他  把你的心交给他
Seduce him. Give him your heart.
挖出来放在他手上
Cut it out and put it in his fucking hands.
亲爱的总统先生
Dear Mr. President,
我正在用我离开桑蒂诺时
I'm writing on an Underwood portable
我父亲给我的安德伍德打字机给您写信
my father gave me when I left for the Sentinel.
我父亲将它给我时说了些话
It was the words my father said when he gave it to me
比这台七十多年的机器更让我能产生共鸣
that have resonated even more than this 70-year-old machine.
"这个安德伍德建立了一个商业帝国"他说
"This Underwood built an empire," He said.
"现在该你去建立一个属于你自己的帝国了"
"Now you go and build one of your own."
这些话一直激励着我
Those words have been a large part of what has motivated my life.
我只用这台打字机写过另一封信
I've only written one other letter with these keys.
那封信不辱使命  希望这次也一样
It did not fail me then. I hope it will not fail me now.
您说我想削弱您
You said I wanted to diminish you.
实际上  我没有
The truth is, I don't.
您说我想在2016年跟您竞争
You said I wanted to challenge you in 2016.
实际上  我没有
The truth is, I don't.
您说我想自己当总统
You said I wanted the presidency for myself.
实际上
The truth is,
我的确想
I do.
哪个政客没想过
What politician hasn't dreamed about what it would be like
宣誓执掌国家最高权力
to take the oath of the highest office of our land?
我曾盯着您的总统办公桌看  觊觎它
I've stared at your desk in the Oval and coveted it.
权力  威望
The power, the prestige.
那些东西对我这样一个来自南卡罗来纳州
Those things have a strong pull on someone like me,
一座小镇  曾一无所有的人来说有致命的吸引力
who came from a small South Carolina town with nothing.
但自您就职时起
But since you assumed office,
我唯一的目标就是为您而战
my only aim has been to fight for you
与您并肩作战
and alongside you,
无论是在国会还是现在
whether that be in Congress or as now,
在这场弹劾之战中
the battle over impeachment.
或许有一天  我有幸能成为总统
Maybe one day I'll have my chance to serve as president,
但绝不是您在任期间
but not while you are the nation's leader.
在您身上  我看到了勇敢
And in you, sir, I see a brave man.
看到了正直  您是我愿意永远追随的总统
A just man. A president whom I would follow anywhere,
无论我们遇到多大的阻力
no matter how strong the wind blows against us.
有一件事我从没对任何人说过
I want to tell you something I have never told anyone:
我13岁那年在谷仓里撞见我父亲
When I was 13 I walked in on my father in the barn.
他把猎枪伸到嘴里
There was a shotgun in his mouth.
他朝我摆了摆手说道"过来  弗兰西斯
He waved me over. "Come here, Francis," He said.
替我扣动扳机"
"Pull the trigger for me."
因为他没有勇气自己做
Because he didn't have the courage to do it himself.
我说"不  爸爸"  就离开了
I said, "No, Papa," And walked out,
我知道他永远没有那个勇气
knowing he would never find that courage.
接下来的七年里  我父亲生不如死
The next seven years were hell for my father,
但我母亲和我更加痛苦
but even more hell for my mother and me.
他令我们都苦不堪言
He made all of us miserable.
酗酒  绝望  暴力
Drinking, despair, violence.
我一生中唯一的后悔  就是当时没扣动扳机
My only regret in life is that I didn't pull that trigger.
死亡对他来说会是种解脱
He would have been better off in the grave,
没有他我们也会过得更好
and we would have been better off without him.
我不会让您陷入同样的境地
I'm not going to put you in the same position
像我父亲对我那样
as my father put me in.
信中附上了一张纸
You will find enclosed on a separate sheet
上面供认了所有您被指控的罪名
a confession to the crimes you have been accused of.
都是假的  但我的签名会使它们成真
They're false words, but my signature will make them true.
有必要的话就用吧
Use them if you must.
如果您真的认为我的所作所为都是为了自己
If you truly believe that I have only served myself,
那么我已经永远失去了您的信任
then I have forever lost your trust.
我现在能做的  只有献出自己的自由以保住您
All I can do now is give you my freedom to save your own.
我说过我会替您承担责任
I said I would take the fall for you,
现在我把方法告诉了您
and now I give you the means to make that happen.
我要自己扣动扳机
I am pulling the trigger myself.
为了实现梦想我们都要做出牺牲
We all must make sacrifices to achieve our dream,
但有时为了大局必须牺牲自己
but sometimes we must sacrifice ourselves for the greater good.
做出这样的牺牲是我的荣幸
It is my honor to make such a sacrifice now.
您忠实的朋友  至少我仍这样认为
Your loyal friend, still in my heart,
即便您不这么想  弗兰西斯
if not in yours, Francis.
宪法列出了一般原则
The Constitution sets forth the general principles --
先生  总统的电话
Sir? The president's on the phone.
总统先生
Mr. President.
我收到信了  我让特莉莎也看了
I got your letter. I had Tricia read it, too.
我很纠结  弗兰克  一半认为你是恳诚的
I'm torn, Frank. Half of me wants to think you're genuine.
另一半却一个字也不信
The other half doesn't trust a word of it.
特莉莎也这么想吗
Does Tricia feel the same way?
她信任克莱尔  所以她也想相信你
She believes in Claire, which inclines her to believe in you.
我字字发自肺腑
I meant every syllable.
我想让您百分之百地相信
I wanted you to know beyond a shadow of a doubt
我愿做任何必要的事
that I am willing to do whatever is necessary.
那么  我为什么抛不开疑虑呢
Well, then why can't I shake the shadow?
因为我是个骗子  先生
Because I'm a liar, sir.
因为我无所顾忌  甚至可以说没有同情心
Because I lack scruples and some would even say compassion.
但那只是我展示给世人的一面
But that's just the image that I present to the world
因为那能使人害怕  让人尊敬我
because it elicits fear and respect.
但我不是那样的人
But it is not who I am.
我希望我的信能向您证明这一点
My hope was that my letter would prove that to you.
好吧  就算你说的都是真的
Well, even if you are being genuine,
对我也没什么用
that doesn't do much for me.
我想躲过弹劾
I won't survive impeachment
不能只靠我和我的副总统关系好
because I got along with my vice president.
是啊  我同意  您需要的不只是我的好意
No, I agree you need more than my good intentions.
证明给我看  弗兰克
Proof. That's what I want to see, Frank.
别光承担责任  我要结果
And not just falling on the sword. Show me results.
那样我会重新考虑你是否值得信任
And then I'll reconsider whether you're worth any of my trust at all.
您是说投票
You're talking votes.
是的  拉票是你的强项
Yeah. Whipping votes was your strong suit.
我想看到你那一面
That's the side of you I want to see.
我已经开始着手了  先生
I've already begun, sir.
是吗  得到票数了吗
Yeah? You have a count?
只有个大概  形势一直在变化
An approximation. The sands keep shifting.
我们能得到众议院的支持吗
Well, can we survive the House or not?
有可能  但是杰姬·夏普在阻挠
Possibly, but Jackie Sharp is making it very difficult.
告诉我票数
Give me numbers.
她需要18票  已经拉到过半
Over half of the 18 that she needs,
所以我想从参议院下手
which is why I'd like to start focusing on the Senate.
你不觉得现在行动有点早吗
Don't you think that's premature?
我们必须有所准备
We should be prepared.
重中之重就是确保您不被定罪
The key battle is making sure that you avoid conviction.
你继续拉票  有消息告诉我
Well, you keep whipping, you keep getting me information,
我就等你电话了
I'll answer your calls.
但别以为你我就此相安无事了  弗兰克
But don't take that as a sign of reconciliation, Frank.
我会感激收获  先生
I'll sing for my supper, sir.
但我不会以为我能不劳而获
I don't expect it for free.
我们明早再商量
Let's talk again tomorrow.
谢谢您  总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
你说你想有选择余地
You said you wanted options.
但弗兰克让我没得选  他坑了我
Frank didn't leave me options. He fucked me.
是你和塔斯克沆瀣一气  先把他坑了
You fucked him first when you sided with Tusk.
但谁管中间过程怎样
But who cares what happened each inning?
只有最终比分才算数
It's the final score that counts.
我在他麾下八年  为他跑前跑后
Eight years I spent busting my ass in this office.
看来还是躲不过为他卖命
I can't seem to escape it.
你是帮我们还是不帮
You gonna help us or not?
我要知道我有什么好处
I need to know what I gain.
-你会得到关照的  -说具体点
- You'll be taking care of. - Specifically.
等到尘埃落定  再看看要怎么办吧
We'll see what makes sense when all the chips have fallen.
那你是要我闷头往悬崖下跳
So you just want me to leap off a cliff
指望着运气好摔不死吗
and hope for a soft landing beneath?
现在谁都不会要你  除了我们
No one will touch you now. Nobody except us.
我们就是你最好的运气
We're as soft as you're gonna get.
能在白宫给我一官半职吗
A job at the White House?
这我说不准
No promises.
结果如何取决于你的
Other than something commensurate
忠诚度和经验
with your loyalty and experience.
我完全可以就此抽身  开始新的生活
I could just walk away from it all. Start a new life.
你抽不了身  你知道你做不到
No, you can't. You know you can't.
离了国会山  你只会衰萎
You'd wither away anywhere but the Hill.
不管你怎么骗自己
It's never been about the money,
你做这一行不是为了钱
no matter what you tell yourself.
我跳槽的时候  弗兰克求我留下
When I left, Frank begged me to stay.
他说"这是权和钱二选一"
"Power versus money," He said.
别屈尊加入那些缴富人税的人
Don't reduce myself to a tax bracket.
他说得对  但我不认为他会求你
He was right. And I doubt he begged.
他对了一半
He was half right.
只要有权力握在手里  就比钱有用
Power is better than money for as long as it lasts.
但权力总会滑出手心
But it never lasts.
你的回答是什么
What's your answer?
你当了党鞭之后变得更冷血了
You've gotten colder since you've taken over this job.
这样办事容易些
It makes things easier.
只是对外吗
On the outside.
内外皆是
And the inside.
我想你  杰姬
I miss you, Jackie.
你打算合作的话  就告诉我
Tell me if you'll cooperate.
你哥哥在议员手下干得如何
How's your brother enjoying working with the congressman?
我接个电话
Oh, excuse me one second.
总统先生
Mr. President.
我要你打给塔斯克  告诉他交易取消
I want you to call Tusk. Tell him the deal is off.
-什么  -你说得对
- What? - You were right.
我不想冒此风险
I don't want to take the risk.
但我已经和他谈过了
But I already spoke to him.
那就再和他谈谈  告诉他特赦没戏了
Well, so speak to him again. And tell him there's no pardon.
先生  我起初对这策略确实有些怀疑
Sir, I -- I -- I was skeptical of this strategy at first,
但我们已经选了这条路  就该走到底
but now that we've gone down this road, we should stick to it.
琳达  你还想回来做幕僚长吗
Linda, do you still want your job back?
当然  先生
Of course, sir.
那就打给他
Then make the call.
我想先看看众议院的结果
I'd rather see what happens in the House
再决定要不要帮你们
before I get involved in any way.
但如果你能表现出对总统坚定的支持
But if you came out vigorously in defense of the President,
可能会让司法委员会觉得...
it might convince the Judiciary Committee --
说实话  我并不是很想
To be honest, I'm not particularly inclined
帮沃克的忙
to be doing Walker any favors.
迈克尔  我知道他撤销了你的国务卿提名
Now, Michael, I know he revoked your nomination.
他完全没有为我争取
He didn't fight for me at all.
他那时刚刚当选  还没有足够的...
Well, he'd just been elected. He wasn't in a position to --
才怪  他明明有这权力
Wrong. He had a clear mandate.
他完全可以支持我
He was in a strong position to defend me.
你说得对
You're right.
如果我是总统  我不会那么轻易放弃
If I had been President I wouldn't have given in so easily.
我会在那篇文章曝光后坚定支持你
I would've stuck by you after that article came to light.
老实说  如果国务卿是你而不是杜兰特
In fact, if you'd been our secretary of state instead of Durant,
我们和中国的关系或许就不会这么差了
I don't think we'd be in the mess we are with China.
但事实是  如果换了我
But the truth is, I wouldn't have
我也不会提名你做国务卿
nominated you for secretary of state in the first place.
我会提名你做财政部长
I would have nominated you for secretary of treasury.
因为你在经济领域的专业知识
Because your expertise in economics is
比你的外交知识强得多
even better than your grasp on foreign affairs.
如果我是总统  你就会做财政部长
No, if I were president, you'd be secretary of treasury.
如果你是总统...
If you were president.
没错
That's right.
你不能这样
You can't do this.
怎么回事
What happened?
是弗兰克捣的鬼吗
Was it Frank?
琳达  听我说
Linda, listen to me --
我明白
I understand.
谢谢你
Thanks.
交易取消了
The deal is off.
她说原因了吗
Did she say why?
没有  只说他改主意了
No. Other than he changed his mind.
但肯定是因为弗兰克
But it must be Frank.
我们还是按原计划来
Then we go back to the original plan.
没错  和以前一样拒不解释
That's right. You plead the Fifth just like you did before.
这就是出政治闹剧
This is political theater.
-我们可以蒙混过关然后关注  -天呐
- We get past it and focus on the - Jesus Christ.
怎么了
What is it?
雷米·丹顿自愿去邓巴那里作证  就是现在
Remy Danton is volunteering to testify to Dunbar, right now.
他自愿的  不是被传唤的吗
He volunteered? He wasn't subpoenaed?
看起来是的
Looks that way.
他要出卖我
He's gonna sell me out.
那样的话他也会遭到起诉
That would open him up to prosecution.
除非他受到了保护
Unless he's being protected.
丹顿在哪
Where's Danton?
我给他助理打电话
I'll call his assistant.
你是否促成外资
Did you or did you not facilitate foreign money
流入政治行动委员会
being funneled into political action committees?
根据我律师的意见
On the advice of my counsel,
我保留行使第五修正案的权利
I reserve my right to invoke the Fifth Amendment.
冯山德声称你不仅是促成了此事
Xander Feng claims you not only facilitated,
更是最初的策划者
you orchestrated the scheme.
你如何回应这项证词
Now what is your response to that testimony?
根据我律师的意见  我保留我的权利
On the advice of my counsel, I reserve my right to --
你今天可以一直保留你的权利  塔斯克先生
You can reserve your right all day long, Mr. Tusk.
但等你面对陪审团时
But when you appear in front of a grand jury,
我确信司法部门一定会起诉你
as I'm sure the Justice Department intends,
你的沉默将使你垮台
your silence will be your downfall.
议员有问题要问吗
Does the congressman have a question?
你可以躲着我们  先生
You can hide from us all you want, sir.
却躲不过与你平起平坐的陪审团
You cannot hide from a jury of your peers.
-主席先生  -就这样吧  我说完了
- Mr. Chairman. - That's it. I'm done.
我放弃我剩余的时间
I relinquish the remainder of my time.
下面交给田纳西州女议员
The chair recognizes the congresswoman from Tennessee.
12分钟  女士
You have 12 minutes, ma'am.
塔斯克先生  我们卷入了与中国的贸易战中
Mr. Tusk, our nation is currently embroiled in a trade war with China.
这严重挫伤了我国经济
It has gutted our economy.
使我们的海军处于险境
It has placed our navy in harm's way.
-而使我们陷入这困境的总统  -他知道
- The president who put us there has -- He knew.
你说什么
Excuse me?
我的委托人保留
My client reserves the --
他知道  你们不就是想知道这个吗
He knew. Isn't that what you're all wondering?
请安静
Quiet, please.
知道什么  确切一些
Knew what, exactly?
有一套机制  它在过去10年里
There was a mechanism by which a great many contributions
贡献了大量的捐助款
were made over the last 10 years.
我仍然认为
The legality of this mechanism is something
这套机制并不触犯法律
that I continue to believe is within the boundaries of the law.
但至于该机制本身  冯山德先生说得对
But as for the mechanism itself, Mr. Feng is correct.
是我策划的  是我促成的
I orchestrated it. I facilitated it.
总统是知道的
And the president knew about it.
丹顿刚刚取消了
Danton just canceled.
去他的吧  我们有塔斯克
Screw Danton. We've got Tusk.
接通司法部长
Get me the attorney general.
没有这个必要  塔斯克先生
That won't be necessary, Mr. Tusk.
请和我们走一趟
If you'll come with us.
真可惜
That's a shame.
手铐也是我遗愿清单中的一项呢
Handcuffs were another item on my bucket list.
这边走  先生  你有权保持沉默
Right this way, sir. You have the right to remain silent.
你所说的一切将用来作为控告你的证据
Anything you say can and will be used against you.
我们谈谈条件吧  他在听证会上很配合
We'll want a bond. For his cooperation in the hearing.
认罪了再谈条件
I'll talk bonds if you'll talk a plea.
人们对证词的反应又快又强烈
Response to the testimony has been swift and vocal.
抗议者从昨天起
Protesters have been gathering in front of
便聚集在白宫前
the White House since yesterday,
要求沃克总统下台
demanding President Walker's resignation.
一份网上请愿书在过去24小时里
And an online petition has already accumulated
已经获得二十多万人签名
over 200,000 signatures in the past 24 hours.
两院公开谴责总统的人数
The list of lawmakers publicly condemning the president
越来越多
has grown on both sides of the aisle.
今天下午  中国大使
And this afternoon the Chinese ambassador
也谴责了沃克政府
also condemned the Walker administration,
指责其瞒着北京与腐败商人做交易
saying China would not negotiate with a president
他说中国不会与这样的总统进行谈判
who dealt with corrupt businessmen behind Beijing's back.
如今  两国的军舰
This at a time when warships from both countries --
与此同时  总统与第一夫人
Meanwhile the president and first lady
仍在戴维营闭门不出  尚未对华盛顿
remain bunkered at Camp David and have offered no public response
最新的进展发表公开回应
to the most recent developments in Washington.
我们请到了《华尔街电讯报》的艾拉·萨伊德
I'm here with Ayla Sayyad of the Wall Street Telegraph.
艾拉  我必须先说
And Ayla, I have to begin by saying that sources
据国会知情人士透露
on the Hill are telling me
司法委员会可能完全跳过辩论
that the Judiciary Committee may bypass debate all together.
不  委员会还没有人正式发表这样的声明
Uh, no one on the committee has gone on record about that.
但如果不是委员会十分倾向于
But do you think these rumors would be circulating
建议众议院启动弹劾程序
if there weren't some sort of strong preference
也不会有这种传言了吧
to recommend the Articles of Impeachment to the House?
我认为几乎可以肯定弹劾很受支持
I think it's safe to assume there is strong support.
我看到的每份民调都显示
Every poll I've seen shows
很大一部分美国人希望更进一步
an overwhelming majority of Americans want this to move forward.
我觉得政客们不会无视这一点
I don't think politicians are going to ignore that.
我已经和我的一些同事聊过了
I've talked to a number of my colleagues already.
民主党这边有些支持者
There's support on my side of the aisle.
-你有多少  -现在包括我在内有五个
- Well, how many do you have? - Five at this point, including me.
那就一共有60个了  还需要七个
That would put us at 60. We'd still need seven more.
你也看了昨晚的民调了
You've seen the overnight polls.
他的支持率都降到个位数了
He's dipped down into the single digits.
你想和我们一起发表公开声明吗
Are you willing to make a public statement with us?
我觉得事到如今
I think the country could use
两党合作一下也不是坏事吧
a little bipartisanship right now, don't you?
你觉得他们在虚张声势吗
Do you think they're bluffing?
为了动摇参议院那些仍在犹豫的人而耍的花招
That it's some sort of stunt to sway the undecideds in the Senate?
迈克尔·科恩小气又记仇  先生
Michael Kern is bitter and small-minded, sir,
但如果他们没获得足够的支持
but he wouldn't appear publicly with Mendoza
他不会和门多萨一同公开表态
if they didn't have the numbers.
可以想象众议院的情况比之前更糟了
Well, I imagine we're worse off in the House than we were before.
其实我本来和杰姬·夏普聊得还挺有成效
In fact, I had a very productive conversation with Jackie Sharp.
她同意停止攻击
She agreed to stop the attack
只要我们在中期选举后支持她做多数党领袖
if we give her our support for majority leader after the midterms.
但雷蒙德一提供他的证词
But once Raymond gave his testimony,
她就打电话说交易取消
she called to say the deal was off.
雷蒙德真的给了我们很大打击
Raymond really has set us back.
我真想不通他为什么要撒谎
I can't fathom why he lied.
他要报复我
Well, it's retribution.
-为了什么  能源危机吗  -不是
- For what? The energy crisis? - No.
您给了他什么好处吗
Did you offer him something?
雷蒙德的证词确实于我们不利
Well, Raymond's testimony hurts,
但并没有终结我们
but it can't finish us off.
谎言是无法证明的
It's impossible to prove a lie.
弹劾不可避免
Impeachment is inevitable.
现在民众舆论成了敌人  事实已经不重要了
Public opinion is the adversary now. Facts no longer matter.
您应该给科恩打个电话  跟他本人聊聊
You should give Kern a call. The personal touch.
如果他重新支持我们
If he came back to us,
别的民主党可能就会胆怯退缩
it might make the other Democrats get cold feet.
中国也在帮倒忙
Well, China isn't helping.
钱主席不回我的电话
President Qian won't return my calls.
北京那边肯定觉得我气数已尽
Beijing must smell death.
他们只是在利用这个局面寻求筹码
They're just exploiting the situation for leverage.
现在先别考虑中国
Let's not worry about China for the moment.
一步一步慢慢来  先生
One battle at a time, sir.
我大概是完了  弗兰克
Maybe I'm finished, Frank.
也许我该接受  我们没法全身而退了
Maybe I need to start accepting that we won't pull out of this.
总统先生  我知道您累了
Mr. President, I know you're tired.
我知道这一切让您备受折磨
I know this has been hell for you.
确实  弹劾会是个严重的打击
And, yes, impeachment would be an awful blow.
我们要在参议院浴血奋战了
We'd have to fight tooth and nail in the Senate.
确实  我们将不得不哀求和妥协
And, yes, we'll have to beg and compromise
重新赚回我们的政治资本
to regain our political capital.
但我们一定会胜利  先生
But we have it in us, sir.
不管拼得多么头破血流
No matter how many scars it leaves us with.
不仅仅是我们  弗兰克
It's not just us, Frank.
还有特莉莎  还有我的孩子们
It's Tricia. It's my children.
我整夜失眠  想着他们看到父亲退缩
I stay awake at night, thinking how much it would crush them,
将是多大的打击
seeing their father hauled off.
先生  不会那样的  我不会允许
Sir, that won't happen because I won't let it.
如果我们遇上最糟的情况
If we're confronted by the worst,
我至少会确保您不会遭受牢狱之灾
I'll make sure you never step foot behind bars.
我向您保证
You have my word on that.
他现在身处黑暗
He's in the darkness now.
我是唯一指路的明灯
And I'm the only beacon of light.
现在只要温柔地把他引向礁石就可以了
Now we gently guide him toward the rocks.
总统先生  您还有我的信
Mr. President, you also still have my letter.
如果您想走那条路  现在还不算太晚
It's not too late, if you want to use that option.
不  你留在国会比待在监狱更有用
No, you're more useful to me on the Hill than in handcuffs.
我会给科恩打电话
I'll call Kern.
-晚安  先生  -晚安
- Goodnight, sir. - Night.
格林告诉你多少
How much did Green tell you?
足够让我现身
Enough that I showed up.
他大概没提到瑞秋·波斯纳  是吧
He probably didn't mention Rachel Posner, huh?
别担心  他不知道
Don't worry. He doesn't know.
但我知道
I do.
你把她藏在乔帕的一间公寓里
You have her in an apartment in Joppa.
我知道你的一举一动
I have your movements.
你有你毁掉手机之前的短信
I have your text messages before you destroyed your phone.
不过这已经足够了
But that's more than enough.
我相信很多人都很想知道她知道的事
I'll bet a lot of people would like to know what she knows.
你给我听好了
Now you listen to me very carefully.
不管你以为你拿到了什么
Whatever you think you've got,
也不管你打算拿这些东西做什么
whatever you intend to do with it,
我不会像格林那样被敲诈牵着走
I don't respond to extortion the same way that Green does.
格林给你的许诺
What Green promised you,
我瞬间就可以抵消
that can be undone in a heartbeat.
所以才把你找来  确保不会变卦
And that's why you're here. Make sure it isn't.
你想要我的保护
You want my protection.
我不信任格林或联调局的任何人
I don't trust Green or anyone at the Bureau.
还有谁知道
Who else knows about this?
没人知道
No one.
我为什么要相信你
Why should I trust you?
因为我们两个都输不起  伙计
'Cause we both have too much to lose, man.
穿上衣服
Get dressed.
你在干什么
What -- what are you doing here?
穿上衣服
Put some clothes on.
为什么
Why -- why?
快点  我们走
Now. Let's go.
有人联系你吗
Did anyone contact you?
你要带我去哪
Where are you taking me?
回答我的问题
Answer my question.
没人联系我
No. Nobody.
有人知道了我们的事
There's someone who knows about us.
知道你在哪
Who knows where you are.
知道我们什么时候见过面
And when we've met.
你是不是要伤害我
Are you gonna hurt me?
你和我说实话就什么事都不会有
Nothing's going to happen if you tell the truth.
我在说实话  没有任何人联系我
I am. I -- I haven't been contacted by anybody.
别再撒谎了  瑞秋
Stop lying, Rachel.
你让我干什么都行
I will do whatever you want.
求你别伤害我
Please, just don't hurt me.
我想让你回答我的问题
What I want is for you to answer my questions,
这样我才能帮你
so I can help you.
你一直以来都在毁掉我的生活
All you have ever done is fuck up my life.
你毁了团契的事
You fucked up the fellowship.
你毁了我和丽萨的感情
You fucked up what I had with Lisa.
即使我都按你说的做了
Even when I did what you asked.
你每次来找我都像变态一样
And your sick fucking visits,
要我哄小孩似的给你读书
and reading to you like a fucking child.
你有什么毛病
What is wrong with you?
为什么你就不能放了我
Why can't you just leave me be?
-为什么你非要这么  -住嘴
- Why do you have to be such a fucking -- - stop!
瑞秋  别做傻事
Rachel? Don't be stupid.
瑞秋
Rachel?
不会有事的
Everything's gonna be fine.
我做的一切都是想保护你
All I've ever done is try to protect you.
我现在也是想保护你
That's what I'm trying to do now.
你要相信我
You have to believe that.
我本来没必要保护你
I didn't have to.
那样事情会简单得多
Been a lot easier if I didn't.
但我还是那样做了  因为我...
But I did. I did it because I --
你干什么
What are you doing?
昨天我们结束了关于
Yesterday we completed hearings with regard to Articles
弹劾美国总统的听证会
of Impeachment for the president of the United States.
主席现在开始听取委员会动议
The chair will now entertain motions from the committee.
主席先生
Mr. Chairman.
主席请阿拉巴马州议员发言
The chair recognizes the congressman from Alabama.
我建议我们直接开始对提议进行投票
I move that we put our recommendation directly to a vote
这样众议院435名成员
so that debate on this important matter may take place
都可以就此事进行辩论
on the House floor, open to all 435 members.
委员会有人反对跳过辩论阶段吗
Are there any objections to bypassing debate in this committee?
现在开始对是否将弹劾状
We will now vote on recommendation of the Articles
送交众议院投票进行表决
of Impeachment to the full House.
同意提议的请喊"赞成"
Those in favor of recommendation say, "Aye."
赞成
Aye.
反对者
Those opposed?
反对
Nay.
赞成占多数
The ayes have it.
委员会正式建议众议院
This committee officially recommends Articles
对弹劾状进行投票
of Impeachment proceed to the House floor.
他来了
He's here.
副总统刚刚到达戴维营
The vice president is just arriving now here at Camp David.
我们预计沃克总统
We except President Walker to speak within the hour,
会在一小时内宣布
announcing his official resignation
辞去美国总统的职务
as president of the United States.
-你怎么样  -我还好
- How are you? - I'm fine.
总统先生
Mr. President.
我在厨房里煮了咖啡
I have coffee in the kitchen.
-要来点吗  -不用了
- Would you like some? - I'm fine.
你马上就要成为
Well, you're about to become
自由世界最有权势的人了
the most powerful man in the free world.
您没必要这么做  先生
You don't have to do this, sir.
我昨晚和科恩谈过了
I spoke to Kern last night.
他不肯让步
He's not gonna back down.
那我们就打败他
So we'll beat him down.
不  弗兰克
No, Frank.
我的支持率只剩8%了
My approvals are at eight percent.
即使我不被定罪  我也没有领导国家的威仪了
Even if I avoid conviction, I have no mandate to lead.
所以我还是有尊严地下台
So better I step aside with some dignity
让国家开始康复
so the nation can start to heal.
我永远无法与您比肩  先生
I can never fill your shoes, sir.
你现在没有选择了
You don't have a choice now.
你的信
Your letter.
好了
Well,
我们去向大家引见美国第46任总统吧
shall we go introduce the 46th president of the United States?
自即日起
Effective immediately,
我辞去美国总统一职
I am resigning the presidency of the United States.
特莉莎和我认为这是最合适的办法
Tricia and I believe that this is the best course of action,
既是为了我们和孩子
not only for us and our children,
更是为了这个国家
but for the country.
我无法否认  这对我们是不幸的一天
It's a sad day for us. I can't deny that.
但让我心有慰藉的是
But I take solace in this:
弗兰克·安德伍德将把美德  经验
Frank Underwood will bring virtue, experience,
和勇气带入总统办公室
and courage to the Oval Office.
由他担任我的副总统  是我的荣幸
I have been blessed to have him as my vice president.
而有他这样的朋友  更是我的幸运
But I'm even more blessed to call him my friend.
能够担任
It has been...
总统一职  服务国家
the greatest honor of my life
是我这一生无上的荣耀
to serve this country as president.
我感谢我的家人  白宫的工作人员
I thank my family, my staff,
以及所有那些支持我的人
and all of those who have supported me.
尽管最近几个月风波不断
Despite the last few months,
但我对祖国的信仰愈发坚定
my faith in this country has never been stronger.
上帝保佑你们
God bless all of you.
上帝保佑美利坚合众国
And god bless the United States of America.
谢谢您的美言  总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President, for those words.
祝您好运  先生
Good luck to you, sir.
先生  请举起右手  跟我宣誓
Sir, please raise your right hand and repeat after me.
本人  弗兰西斯·J·安德伍德
I, Francis J. Underwood...
在此庄严宣誓
Do solemnly swear...
总统先生
Mr. President.
国务卿女士
Madam Secretary.
内阁其余成员都在白宫等您
The rest of the Cabinet is awaiting you at the White House.
我们希望马上为您做国家安全简报  长官
We'd like to give you a national security briefing right away, sir.
详情我都知道
I'm aware of the particulars.
请联系一下北京
Can you please get Beijing on the phone?
钱主席已经两天没回过总统的电话了
Qian hasn't returned the President's calls for two days.
现在总统换人了
Well, there's a new president now.
马上给他打电话
Please get him on the line.
两个小时前  作为三军统帅
Two hours ago, President Underwood,
安德伍德总统下达了第一道命令
in his first act as commander in chief,
他要求第七舰队撤出日本周边海域
gave orders to the seventh fleet to vacate Japanese waters.
这得益于总统与钱主席进行的一次
This was a result of a productive conversation
颇有成效的对话
with President Qian,
而钱主席也对该海域的
who gave similar orders
中国舰队下达了撤退的命令
to Chinese naval vessels in the same region.
他行动挺快啊
He moves quick.
你是说对中国人  还是对沃克
Do you mean with the Chinese or with Walker?
-冯先生  -怎么了
- Mr. Feng? - What is it?
我们是司法部的  请随我们走一趟
U.S. Justice Department. We need you to come with us.
-去哪  -你将被遣返回中国
- Where? - You're going back to China.
我申请了政治避难
I have asylum.
不  先生  你的避难请求已经被驳回了
No, sir, you don't. Your asylum has been rescinded.
我有书面证明  无条件无限期的庇护
I have it in writing. Unconditional and permanent.
先生  我说过了  对你的庇护已经作废了
Sir, I'm telling you, your asylum has been rescinded.
请收拾个人物品  跟我们走
Now, please, gather your things and come with us.
驳回他的避难不是没有后果的
Revoking his asylum will have consequences.
但是法律上没问题吧
But we're solid from a legal perspective?
法律上没问题  他的文件还没进入批准流程
Legally yes. His initial paperwork hasn't been processed,
我们可以声称他对我国利益构成威胁
and we can claim he poses a threat to our national interests.
但这会削弱国务院的信誉
But it diminishes the integrity of our State Department.
哪一个更重要  凯茜  信誉还是和平
What's more important, Cathy? Integrity or peace?
你知道他会被处决的
You know they'll execute him.
中国人说对了一件事
The Chinese are right about one thing.
有时候  就得舍弃一人  保证全局
Sometimes you have to sacrifice the one for the many.
我们回华盛顿吧
Let's get back to Washington.
好的  请及时通知我  非常感谢
Okay. Please let me know. Thanks very much.
-有消息吗  -还是没有
- Anything? - Not yet.
你看看能不能通过戒酒互助会查到他的行踪
See if you can track down anyone from his regular AA meetings.
我和辅导员谈过了
I spoke to the moderator.
他说已经有好几周没见过道格了
He said he hasn't seen Doug in several weeks.
我查过医院  问过他的房东
I checked all the hospitals, his landlord...
先生  人都到齐了
Sir, everyone's here.
好  等手头事一过
All right, when this is all over
你和南茜一起找道格
I want you to work with Nancy on finding Doug.
我已经和特区警察局打过招呼
I've already alerted the D.C. Metro.
他们会对他的车牌发布全境通告
They put out an APB on his car.
我们会找到他的  先生
We'll find him, sir.
克莱尔呢
Claire?
就在外面
Just outside.
咱们走  南茜
Let's go, Nancy.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentleman,
有请总统先生和第一夫人
the President and the first lady.
弗兰西斯
Francis,
我知道离你生日还有段时间
I know your birthday isn't for a couple weeks,
但我要送你一份礼物
but I got you something.
-这是干什么  -打开嘛
- What's this? - Open it.
我让人新做了一个
I had a new one made.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
你进去吧
You go ahead.
一起来吧
Come on.
这是我们共同努力的结果
We earned this together.
你先自己去  好好享受一下
Take a few moments for yourself first.
我就在外面
I'll be out here.
1789年4月21日  美国第一任副总统约翰·亚当斯在纽约宣誓就职时
当选总统乔治·华盛顿还在赶往临时首都的路上
直到4月30日才正式就任  所以在30日之前的9天里
亚当斯作为副总统就成了这个年轻国家的最高行政长官
美国是先有有副总统  后有总统的
美国历史上  曾有9位副总统因总统亡故或辞职而接任成为总统
1973年  美国副总统阿格纽因贪腐被调查而被迫辞职
来自密西根州的众议员福特被时任总统的尼克松任命为副总统
次年  尼克松因水门事件被迫辞职  福特成为美国第38任总统
福特未经民主选举就担任过副总统和总统的职位
翻译  卫老哥
翻译  某豚
翻译  章鱼X
翻译  艾瑞卡
翻译  冬麟
翻译  香茗小焙
时间轴  吉吉
后期  饿得慌
特效  宝宝
顾问  老杜
校对  草草
总监  草草
纸牌屋
第二季  第十三集
人人影视倾情奉献